[{"pokedexNumber":1,"name":"bulbasaur","type":"grass","speed":45,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p1.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/1.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/1.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/1.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":2,"name":"ivysaur","type":"grass","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p2.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/2.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/2.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/2.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":3,"name":"venusaur","type":"grass","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p3.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/3.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/3.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/3.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":4,"name":"charmander","type":"fire","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p4.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/4.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/4.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/4.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":5,"name":"charmeleon","type":"fire","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p5.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/5.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/5.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/5.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":6,"name":"charizard","type":"fire","speed":100,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p6.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/6.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/6.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/6.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":7,"name":"squirtle","type":"water","speed":43,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p7.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/7.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/7.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/7.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":8,"name":"wartortle","type":"water","speed":58,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p8.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/8.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/8.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/8.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":9,"name":"blastoise","type":"water","speed":78,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p9.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/9.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/9.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/9.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":37,"name":"vulpix","type":"fire","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p37.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/37.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/37.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/37.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":38,"name":"ninetales","type":"fire","speed":100,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p38.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/38.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/38.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/38.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":43,"name":"oddish","type":"grass","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p43.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/43.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/43.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/43.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":44,"name":"gloom","type":"grass","speed":40,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p44.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/44.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/44.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/44.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":45,"name":"vileplume","type":"grass","speed":50,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p45.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/45.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/45.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/45.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":54,"name":"psyduck","type":"water","speed":55,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p54.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/54.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/54.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/54.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":55,"name":"golduck","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p55.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/55.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/55.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/55.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":58,"name":"growlithe","type":"fire","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p58.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/58.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/58.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/58.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":59,"name":"arcanine","type":"fire","speed":95,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p59.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/59.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/59.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/59.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":60,"name":"poliwag","type":"water","speed":90,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p60.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/60.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/60.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/60.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":61,"name":"poliwhirl","type":"water","speed":90,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p61.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/61.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/61.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/61.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":62,"name":"poliwrath","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p62.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/62.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/62.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/62.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":69,"name":"bellsprout","type":"grass","speed":40,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p69.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/69.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/69.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/69.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":70,"name":"weepinbell","type":"grass","speed":55,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p70.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/70.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/70.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/70.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":71,"name":"victreebel","type":"grass","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p71.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/71.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/71.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/71.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":72,"name":"tentacool","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p72.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/72.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/72.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/72.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":73,"name":"tentacruel","type":"water","speed":100,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p73.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/73.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/73.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/73.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":77,"name":"ponyta","type":"fire","speed":90,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p77.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/77.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/77.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/77.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":78,"name":"rapidash","type":"fire","speed":105,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p78.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/78.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/78.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/78.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":79,"name":"slowpoke","type":"water","speed":15,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p79.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/79.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/79.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/79.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":80,"name":"slowbro","type":"water","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p80.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/80.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/80.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/80.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":86,"name":"seel","type":"water","speed":45,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p86.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/86.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/86.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/86.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":87,"name":"dewgong","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p87.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/87.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/87.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/87.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":90,"name":"shellder","type":"water","speed":40,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p90.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/90.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/90.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/90.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":91,"name":"cloyster","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p91.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/91.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/91.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/91.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":98,"name":"krabby","type":"water","speed":50,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p98.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/98.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/98.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/98.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":99,"name":"kingler","type":"water","speed":75,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p99.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/99.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/99.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/99.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":102,"name":"exeggcute","type":"grass","speed":40,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p102.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/102.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/102.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/102.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":103,"name":"exeggutor","type":"grass","speed":55,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p103.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/103.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/103.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/103.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":114,"name":"tangela","type":"grass","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p114.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/114.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/114.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/114.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":116,"name":"horsea","type":"water","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p116.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/116.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/116.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/116.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":117,"name":"seadra","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p117.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/117.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/117.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/117.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":118,"name":"goldeen","type":"water","speed":63,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p118.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/118.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/118.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/118.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":119,"name":"seaking","type":"water","speed":68,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p119.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/119.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/119.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/119.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":120,"name":"staryu","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p120.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/120.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/120.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/120.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":121,"name":"starmie","type":"water","speed":115,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p121.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/121.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/121.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/121.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":126,"name":"magmar","type":"fire","speed":93,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p126.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/126.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/126.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/126.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":129,"name":"magikarp","type":"water","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p129.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/129.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/129.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/129.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":130,"name":"gyarados","type":"water","speed":81,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p130.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/130.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/130.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/130.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":131,"name":"lapras","type":"water","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p131.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/131.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/131.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/131.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":134,"name":"vaporeon","type":"water","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p134.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/134.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/134.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/134.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":136,"name":"flareon","type":"fire","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p136.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/136.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/136.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/136.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":146,"name":"moltres","type":"fire","speed":90,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p146.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/146.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/146.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/146.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":152,"name":"chikorita","type":"grass","speed":45,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p152.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/152.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/152.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/152.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":153,"name":"bayleef","type":"grass","speed":60,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p153.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/153.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/153.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/153.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":154,"name":"meganium","type":"grass","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p154.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/154.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/154.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/154.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":155,"name":"cyndaquil","type":"fire","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p155.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/155.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/155.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/155.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":156,"name":"quilava","type":"fire","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p156.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/156.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/156.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/156.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":157,"name":"typhlosion","type":"fire","speed":100,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p157.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/157.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/157.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/157.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":158,"name":"totodile","type":"water","speed":43,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p158.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/158.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/158.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/158.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":159,"name":"croconaw","type":"water","speed":58,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p159.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/159.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/159.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/159.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":160,"name":"feraligatr","type":"water","speed":78,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p160.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/160.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/160.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/160.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":170,"name":"chinchou","type":"water","speed":67,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p170.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/170.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/170.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/170.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":171,"name":"lanturn","type":"water","speed":67,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p171.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/171.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/171.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/171.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":182,"name":"bellossom","type":"grass","speed":50,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p182.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/182.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/182.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/182.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":183,"name":"marill","type":"water","speed":40,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p183.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/183.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/183.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/183.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":184,"name":"azumarill","type":"water","speed":50,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p184.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/184.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/184.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/184.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":186,"name":"politoed","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p186.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/186.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/186.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/186.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":187,"name":"hoppip","type":"grass","speed":50,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p187.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/187.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/187.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/187.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":188,"name":"skiploom","type":"grass","speed":80,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p188.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/188.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/188.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/188.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":189,"name":"jumpluff","type":"grass","speed":110,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p189.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/189.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/189.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/189.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":191,"name":"sunkern","type":"grass","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p191.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/191.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/191.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/191.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":192,"name":"sunflora","type":"grass","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p192.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/192.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/192.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/192.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":194,"name":"wooper","type":"water","speed":15,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p194.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/194.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/194.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/194.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":195,"name":"quagsire","type":"water","speed":35,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p195.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/195.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/195.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/195.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":199,"name":"slowking","type":"water","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p199.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/199.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/199.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/199.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":211,"name":"qwilfish","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p211.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/211.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/211.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/211.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":218,"name":"slugma","type":"fire","speed":20,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p218.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/218.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/218.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/218.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":219,"name":"magcargo","type":"fire","speed":30,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p219.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/219.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/219.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/219.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":222,"name":"corsola","type":"water","speed":35,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p222.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/222.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/222.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/222.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":223,"name":"remoraid","type":"water","speed":65,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p223.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/223.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/223.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/223.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":224,"name":"octillery","type":"water","speed":45,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p224.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/224.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/224.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/224.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":226,"name":"mantine","type":"water","speed":70,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p226.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/226.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/226.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/226.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":230,"name":"kingdra","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p230.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/230.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/230.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/230.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":240,"name":"magby","type":"fire","speed":83,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p240.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/240.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/240.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/240.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":244,"name":"entei","type":"fire","speed":100,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p244.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/244.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/244.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/244.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":245,"name":"suicune","type":"water","speed":85,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p245.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/245.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/245.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/245.gif"},{"pokedexNumber":250,"name":"ho-oh","type":"fire","speed":90,"img3d":"https://images.gameinfo.io/pokemon-trimmed/60/p250.webp","imgSvg":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/dream-world/250.svg","imgFront":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/250.gif","imgBack":"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/versions/generation-v/black-white/animated/back/250.gif"}]